[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average lifespan of a lion living in the wild?", "correct_answer": "10 -15 years", "incorrect_answers": ["20 - 30 years", "Less than 10 years", "Greater than 30 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of  the following statements is true about mosquitoes?", "correct_answer": "Only female mosquitoes suck blood.", "incorrect_answers": ["Only male mosquitoes suck blood.", "All mosquitoes on the planet drink blood.", "Only baby mosquitoes drink blood."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1982 movie Creepshow was a combination of 5 individual stories. Which of the following is NOT one of the titles?", "correct_answer": "The Tide Is High", "incorrect_answers": ["Theyre Creeping Up On You", "Fathers Day", "The Lonely Death of Jordy Verril"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In average conditions, approximately how many hours does it take for the dead bodys temperature to equalize with the surrounding environment?", "correct_answer": "24", "incorrect_answers": ["12", "48", "26"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these people was nicknamed The Iron Butterfly?", "correct_answer": "Imelda Marcos", "incorrect_answers": ["Indira Gandhi", "Margaret Thatcher", "Bella Abzug"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the drama movie 21, Ben is asked to join the card counting group and immediately agrees.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest living subspecies of giraffe on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Masai Giraffe", "incorrect_answers": ["South African Giraffe", "Rothschild Giraffe", "Nubian Giraffe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Roses brother, the minister, in the movie, The African Queen?", "correct_answer": "Robert Morley", "incorrect_answers": ["Richard Morley", "Robert Guiness", "Robert Taylor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Leonardo DiCaprio mostly interested in back when he was a child?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Comic books", "Museums", "Baseball cards"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can you donate any electrical items to a recycling dump place?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two landlocked countries are surrounded by other landlocked countries?", "correct_answer": "Liechtenstein and Uzbekistan", "incorrect_answers": ["Austria and Switzerland", "Tajikistan and Liechtenstein", "Switzerland and Tajikistan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 1978 film, Doctor Sam Loomis is the psychiatrist who takes care of Michael Myers at Smiths Grove-Warren County Sanitarium in Illinois.", "correct_answer": "Halloween", "incorrect_answers": ["The Amityville Horror", "Dawn of the Dead", "The Omen"]}]